[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "Any thoughts?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "thoughts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Topanga Canyon", "California"]}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Where were you when you heard the news and what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "you", "heard", "the", "news", "and", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "I woke up in my -- I live in Topanga Canyon in California and I woke up and unfortunately I heard it on Facebook.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "woke", "up", "in", "my", "--", "I", "live", "in", "Topanga", "Canyon", "in", "California", "and", "I", "woke", "up", "and", "unfortunately", "I", "heard", "it", "on", "Facebook", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "You take drugs?", "question_tokens": ["You", "take", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "How have you managed to do that and why do you think Philip in the end was unable to battle those demons successfully?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "managed", "to", "do", "that", "and", "why", "do", "you", "think", "Philip", "in", "the", "end", "was", "unable", "to", "battle", "those", "demons", "successfully", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "I don't know, I mean it's a hard question to ask me because I've never gone through that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "I", "mean", "it", "'s", "a", "hard", "question", "to", "ask", "me", "because", "I", "'ve", "never", "gone", "through", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Philip"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Do you understand that pressure and do you think that certain types of addicted personalities succumb perhaps to that particular pressure that comes with performing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "that", "pressure", "and", "do", "you", "think", "that", "certain", "types", "of", "addicted", "personalities", "succumb", "perhaps", "to", "that", "particular", "pressure", "that", "comes", "with", "performing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Philip"]}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Why that scene?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "that", "scene", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, my friends and I really, really love this movie and we had -- since I worked on \"Almost Famous\" with Philip I started to kind of realize what an incredible, like you said, character actor he was.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "friends", "and", "I", "really", ",", "really", "love", "this", "movie", "and", "we", "had", "--", "since", "I", "worked", "on", "``", "Almost", "Famous", "''", "with", "Philip", "I", "started", "to", "kind", "of", "realize", "what", "an", "incredible", ",", "like", "you", "said", ",", "character", "actor", "he", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "How would you like him to be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "him", "to", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "UGIT: Well, the way I remember him is that strength of professionalism and that strength of character.", "answer_tokens": ["UGIT", ":", "Well", ",", "the", "way", "I", "remember", "him", "is", "that", "strength", "of", "professionalism", "and", "that", "strength", "of", "character", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Do you think like many, many people that work with Philip Seymour Hoffman that your own acting significantly improve through the process of just being in the same room as him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "like", "many", ",", "many", "people", "that", "work", "with", "Philip", "Seymour", "Hoffman", "that", "your", "own", "acting", "significantly", "improve", "through", "the", "process", "of", "just", "being", "in", "the", "same", "room", "as", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Philip Seymour Hoffman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "It's a bloody waste, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "bloody", "waste", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "When's that out?", "question_tokens": ["When", "'s", "that", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Apparently later this year, fall.", "answer_tokens": ["Apparently", "later", "this", "year", ",", "fall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "CD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", ",", "RBR", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Do you feel that the public opinion towards scandals like this is slightly worked by the celebrity element and it was different to how it would be if there was no celebrity involved?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "the", "public", "opinion", "towards", "scandals", "like", "this", "is", "slightly", "worked", "by", "the", "celebrity", "element", "and", "it", "was", "different", "to", "how", "it", "would", "be", "if", "there", "was", "no", "celebrity", "involved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "I think there's a lot more opinion if there's a celebrity, not necessarily one way or the other, just a lot more emotion, more opinion all the way around.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "more", "opinion", "if", "there", "'s", "a", "celebrity", ",", "not", "necessarily", "one", "way", "or", "the", "other", ",", "just", "a", "lot", "more", "emotion", ",", "more", "opinion", "all", "the", "way", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "What do you make of the Woody Allen scandals, what's your personal opinion?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "Woody", "Allen", "scandals", ",", "what", "'s", "your", "personal", "opinion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I just think it's, you know, I feel like it's sad to see this family go through this.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "think", "it", "'s", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "feel", "like", "it", "'s", "sad", "to", "see", "this", "family", "go", "through", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Woody Allen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "You're on view of Polanski over the years appears to have softened slightly in the sense that you -- I don't know, is it too far to say you've forgiven him or you are just less angry about it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "on", "view", "of", "Polanski", "over", "the", "years", "appears", "to", "have", "softened", "slightly", "in", "the", "sense", "that", "you", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "is", "it", "too", "far", "to", "say", "you", "'ve", "forgiven", "him", "or", "you", "are", "just", "less", "angry", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I have forgiven him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "forgiven", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Polanski"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What do you feel about the fact that Roman Polanski just fled the country and has never actually had to face justice for what happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "Roman", "Polanski", "just", "fled", "the", "country", "and", "has", "never", "actually", "had", "to", "face", "justice", "for", "what", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, he wasn't facing justice.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "was", "n't", "facing", "justice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "MD", "RB", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Tell me, do you see a certain irony in that?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", ",", "do", "you", "see", "a", "certain", "irony", "in", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "I see a big irony in that because, you know, I have no hard feelings against any of his famous friends, who wrote those letters, couldn't believed what he did, and we're standing up for someone they cared about.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "see", "a", "big", "irony", "in", "that", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "have", "no", "hard", "feelings", "against", "any", "of", "his", "famous", "friends", ",", "who", "wrote", "those", "letters", ",", "could", "n't", "believed", "what", "he", "did", ",", "and", "we", "'re", "standing", "up", "for", "someone", "they", "cared", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What was your reaction when you read it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "read", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I was surprised and happy he sent it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "surprised", "and", "happy", "he", "sent", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "What advice would you give?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, my advice would first be, this is a really serious matter and bringing it up on Twitter is probably not the best idea.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "advice", "would", "first", "be", ",", "this", "is", "a", "really", "serious", "matter", "and", "bringing", "it", "up", "on", "Twitter", "is", "probably", "not", "the", "best", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "At what point did you change your name?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "point", "did", "you", "change", "your", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "I think from -- it was a series of little-bitty stuffs which I do detailed in the book.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "from", "--", "it", "was", "a", "series", "of", "little-bitty", "stuffs", "which", "I", "do", "detailed", "in", "the", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "But when you began wearing the girl's clothes at school, was that when you began calling yourself Janet or was it after you had the operation when you're 18?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "began", "wearing", "the", "girl", "'s", "clothes", "at", "school", ",", "was", "that", "when", "you", "began", "calling", "yourself", "Janet", "or", "was", "it", "after", "you", "had", "the", "operation", "when", "you", "'re", "18", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "It was way before that.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "way", "before", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Janet"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beyonce"]}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "So I'm seeing a bit of Janet and a bit of Beyonce, especially with the hair?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "'m", "seeing", "a", "bit", "of", "Janet", "and", "a", "bit", "of", "Beyonce", ",", "especially", "with", "the", "hair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Oh, I live for Beyonce.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "live", "for", "Beyonce", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Janet"], "LOCATION": ["Beyonce"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Well, that was a big step and a long journey, right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "was", "a", "big", "step", "and", "a", "long", "journey", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Was there a moment, was it immediately afterwards or was it a month, a year?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "a", "moment", ",", "was", "it", "immediately", "afterwards", "or", "was", "it", "a", "month", ",", "a", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I think it actually came before it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "actually", "came", "before", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "When you first got to New York City, what was that to you after all you've been through to get to this thriving harbor (ph) of all types of people?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "first", "got", "to", "New", "York", "City", ",", "what", "was", "that", "to", "you", "after", "all", "you", "'ve", "been", "through", "to", "get", "to", "this", "thriving", "harbor", "(", "ph", ")", "of", "all", "types", "of", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I think New York was a part -- the third part of my dream.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "New", "York", "was", "a", "part", "--", "the", "third", "part", "of", "my", "dream", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "When you have told these men the news, did some of them run in wild, did others surprised you but being very supportive, I mean, how did men react?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "have", "told", "these", "men", "the", "news", ",", "did", "some", "of", "them", "run", "in", "wild", ",", "did", "others", "surprised", "you", "but", "being", "very", "supportive", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "how", "did", "men", "react", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NNS", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "NNS", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "They were all very mixed.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "were", "all", "very", "mixed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "How did he react?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "he", "react", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "It was a -- it was a pivotal moment.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "--", "it", "was", "a", "pivotal", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Would you like to get married?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "get", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Yeah, I would, you know, one day, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "would", ",", "you", "know", ",", "one", "day", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "There's a time he questioned you?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "time", "he", "questioned", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Not yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["E.E. Cummings"]}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Somebody's watching here who might be like a young Charles and still feel they can't go through with this that feel desperate, they want to be woman, what's the best advice you would give them?", "question_tokens": ["Somebody", "'s", "watching", "here", "who", "might", "be", "like", "a", "young", "Charles", "and", "still", "feel", "they", "ca", "n't", "go", "through", "with", "this", "that", "feel", "desperate", ",", "they", "want", "to", "be", "woman", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "best", "advice", "you", "would", "give", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "VBG", "RB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "I think the hardest battle that any of us can fight as E.E. Cummings says is the battle of being ourselves in a world that tells us that we are wrong, that we should be silence and that we shouldn't be ourselves.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "hardest", "battle", "that", "any", "of", "us", "can", "fight", "as", "E.E.", "Cummings", "says", "is", "the", "battle", "of", "being", "ourselves", "in", "a", "world", "that", "tells", "us", "that", "we", "are", "wrong", ",", "that", "we", "should", "be", "silence", "and", "that", "we", "should", "n't", "be", "ourselves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "When you're seeing issues like gay marriage, in particular, moving very fast in America, it's possible that many people imagined was possible, what does that tell you about modern America and its ability, perhaps, to become much more accepting and tolerant than may have been even 20 years ago?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "seeing", "issues", "like", "gay", "marriage", ",", "in", "particular", ",", "moving", "very", "fast", "in", "America", ",", "it", "'s", "possible", "that", "many", "people", "imagined", "was", "possible", ",", "what", "does", "that", "tell", "you", "about", "modern", "America", "and", "its", "ability", ",", "perhaps", ",", "to", "become", "much", "more", "accepting", "and", "tolerant", "than", "may", "have", "been", "even", "20", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RBR", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I think that that movement has been going on for a very long time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "that", "movement", "has", "been", "going", "on", "for", "a", "very", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bible"]}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Who is responsible for this massive snow storm raging across America, God or Science?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "responsible", "for", "this", "massive", "snow", "storm", "raging", "across", "America", ",", "God", "or", "Science", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Actually, you know, the Bible tells us the whole creation is running down because man's fool and then so we do have extremes in weather patters today.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "Bible", "tells", "us", "the", "whole", "creation", "is", "running", "down", "because", "man", "'s", "fool", "and", "then", "so", "we", "do", "have", "extremes", "in", "weather", "patters", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Ham"]}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "I mean, did you learn anything which was even remotely persuasive to you that maybe you're barking up the wrong tree about this whole global warming business?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "did", "you", "learn", "anything", "which", "was", "even", "remotely", "persuasive", "to", "you", "that", "maybe", "you", "'re", "barking", "up", "the", "wrong", "tree", "about", "this", "whole", "global", "warming", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "No and let me say just inherent in Mr. Ham's and so first of all, it was very respectful evening.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "and", "let", "me", "say", "just", "inherent", "in", "Mr.", "Ham", "'s", "and", "so", "first", "of", "all", ",", "it", "was", "very", "respectful", "evening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["fall"]}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "If there's even 1 percent chance that it does exist and given the 80 percent of scientist often keep does or want to say the chance is a much higher, but even if you believe your version and it's all a load of hoeey, is it really helpful to anybody to be just take a risk and do nothing?", "question_tokens": ["If", "there", "'s", "even", "1", "percent", "chance", "that", "it", "does", "exist", "and", "given", "the", "80", "percent", "of", "scientist", "often", "keep", "does", "or", "want", "to", "say", "the", "chance", "is", "a", "much", "higher", ",", "but", "even", "if", "you", "believe", "your", "version", "and", "it", "'s", "all", "a", "load", "of", "hoeey", ",", "is", "it", "really", "helpful", "to", "anybody", "to", "be", "just", "take", "a", "risk", "and", "do", "nothing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "CC", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJR", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "By the way, I just want to say to Bill, too, that, you know, some of the catastrophic things that happen and the terrible things that happened in the world even death, in fact that we die, is because of the fall and not because of the flood but, you know, first of all, you know, the debate tonight was not about global warming, it wasn't about climate change.", "answer_tokens": ["By", "the", "way", ",", "I", "just", "want", "to", "say", "to", "Bill", ",", "too", ",", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "some", "of", "the", "catastrophic", "things", "that", "happen", "and", "the", "terrible", "things", "that", "happened", "in", "the", "world", "even", "death", ",", "in", "fact", "that", "we", "die", ",", "is", "because", "of", "the", "fall", "and", "not", "because", "of", "the", "flood", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "debate", "tonight", "was", "not", "about", "global", "warming", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "about", "climate", "change", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent", "80 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Well, what do you believe in?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "do", "you", "believe", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "I didn't tell you what I believe about global warming.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "tell", "you", "what", "I", "believe", "about", "global", "warming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam"], "LOCATION": ["Bible"]}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CD", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CD", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Did you believe Ken, do you believe as I'm led to believe you believe that dinosaurs and man coexisted?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "believe", "Ken", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "as", "I", "'m", "led", "to", "believe", "you", "believe", "that", "dinosaurs", "and", "man", "coexisted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Actually, based on the Bible, I believe that all the land animals are made on day 6 and Adam and Eve were made on day 6 and, you know, people try to make fun of us believing that we believe that dinosaurs live with people but there's a lot of animals alive today that according to evolutions has lived with dinosaurs and some of them like crocodiles and for instance horseshoe crabs supposedly evolve before dinosaurs may live today with people.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "based", "on", "the", "Bible", ",", "I", "believe", "that", "all", "the", "land", "animals", "are", "made", "on", "day", "6", "and", "Adam", "and", "Eve", "were", "made", "on", "day", "6", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "people", "try", "to", "make", "fun", "of", "us", "believing", "that", "we", "believe", "that", "dinosaurs", "live", "with", "people", "but", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "animals", "alive", "today", "that", "according", "to", "evolutions", "has", "lived", "with", "dinosaurs", "and", "some", "of", "them", "like", "crocodiles", "and", "for", "instance", "horseshoe", "crabs", "supposedly", "evolve", "before", "dinosaurs", "may", "live", "today", "with", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ken"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Are you suggesting that man existed 17 million years ago?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "suggesting", "that", "man", "existed", "17", "million", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "No, I'm not saying 17 million years and you said you find dinosaur bones with the labels on them, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "saying", "17", "million", "years", "and", "you", "said", "you", "find", "dinosaur", "bones", "with", "the", "labels", "on", "them", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 536, "question": "How can there be like from stars that are more than 6,000 light years away and so on?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "there", "be", "like", "from", "stars", "that", "are", "more", "than", "6,000", "light", "years", "away", "and", "so", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "And we had some of these things in the debate as, you know, and, you know, even looking a tree rings, you have to make assumptions, was it one-year, two-year or whatever and even matching up different trees has assumptions involved in how they match those rings together and I said --", "answer_tokens": ["And", "we", "had", "some", "of", "these", "things", "in", "the", "debate", "as", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "even", "looking", "a", "tree", "rings", ",", "you", "have", "to", "make", "assumptions", ",", "was", "it", "one-year", ",", "two-year", "or", "whatever", "and", "even", "matching", "up", "different", "trees", "has", "assumptions", "involved", "in", "how", "they", "match", "those", "rings", "together", "and", "I", "said", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]